If I wanted to track the number of wheels on my car, and if you are working in a file so
that you can follow along with me, let me show you what I typed into the Ripple.
In cars is the name of my P-Wi file without the P-Wi extension, just so you have that
there.
If I want to be able to access these class variables in my methods, I can provide something
called a class method.
Those are defined with decorator like this.
I'm not going to go into too much detail.
I just want to show you because you might see this in other code.
The thing about the class method, a class method doesn't take self.
Instead, it takes a different argument called CLS, or it doesn't really matter what
you name it, but this is the convention.
Now you can access these class variables.
Oops, I want to return the number of wheels variable.
Just saving that and reloading it.
You can say my Subaru is a car, a car, Subaru.
That's my instance.
I wasn't able to access the name from the just the type.
But now, because I made this a class method, I can say cars.car and call get number of wheels.
Notice this is the type, not the instance.
It's the difference between a class method and an instance method.
As you're just starting out, you'll probably be using all instance methods, class methods,
or generally for special cases.
You can also call these class methods on an instance because the instance knows about the class,
but not kind of the other way around.
So I still can't call .start.
This is expecting an instance.
I don't have one, and I'm going to get an error.
That's a start is missing one required positional argument of self.
Now you kind of know what some of these errors mean, where self is appearing from,
being binded under the hood by Python.